

Le Thi Binh

Date of birth Jan 17, 1999 Gender Female

Phone 0393 367 160

Email lebinh99pt@gmail.com

Address Xuan Dinh, Bac Tu Liem, Ha Noi

PROFILE

I have graduated in English at Phuong Dong university. I am looking forward to finding job related to English in reputed company, having challenge to gain more experience and knowledge. Impressed Quote "A winner never stops trying" I try my best at all times and I believe that I can complete the mission well.

EDUCATION

Sep 2017 – Now Phuong Dong university.

Major: English

Sep 2014 – May 2017 Studied at Long Chau Sa high school.

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2020 – Jan 2021

EZPAGE COMPANY CUSTOMER CARE STAFF

- Perform to advertisement translation and post on the company's website, fan page.
- Providing consultation, introduction to customers via email or fan page.
- Collecting and aggregate information related to customer orders and send to leader.

Jul 2018 - Jun 2020

CONVIENCE STORE EMPLOYEE

Part-time staff in convenience store near university.

- Organizing the good on shelves.
- To be responsible for cashier.
- Make reports of sales every day.

Aug 2017 – May 2018

BLUE STAR TALENT TRAINING CENTER EMPLOYEE

- Prepare learning tools for student.
- Take attendance of students before class time.
- Providing course's consultation and introduction to parents and student.

SKILLS

Languages English, Chinese.

Computer Word, Excel, PowerPoint.

Soft Skills Teamwork, Presentation, Positive Attitude.

HONORS & AWARDS

2020 Phuong Dong university scholarship

2015 District level excellent student contest (Literature subject)

REFERENCES

Vu Thi Thanh Yen, English Department Head in Phuong Dong university.

Email: yenvu1978@gmail.com

Phone: 0979-050-678

INTERESTS

Cooking, Reading, Traveling.